Hello friends, see in
this video how to install the Oil Tech Care Insurance app on your mobile.
First of all, you have to
go to the Play Store and search for Oil Tech Care Insurance app.
As you search, it will
appear in such an icon, after that you have to
install it, like
after the installation is complete, open it. After opening, such a
screen will come, you will
see a skip in the screen, so
you have to skip here,
after that you have to type the mobile number here.
After entering the mobile number, a page will
open in which the option of first name, last name and
date of birth will come,
after writing this you have to go to date of birth,
there will be year, month and date,
after selecting it you have to go to done,
then in this way you have to type your email ID here
below, after that a tick option will
come, after ticking you have to go to continue, in this
way an OTP will come on your mobile which
you have to type here,
after that a window will open in which first of all there is an
orange colored buy policy and below there is an add
policy option, if you want to buy then you
can buy policy and add us  If you have an employee then you have to go to
Add below, then this way the interface
will open in which first the company will be visible and there will be
me, if you have bought personal insurance then you have to go
to me and here you have to
enter the policy number, card number and date of birth,
if the company has given you health insurance then you have to
go to the company and here first of all you have to
search the name of the company at the top, if
you type three or four letters then the
name of your company will be visible, then below you have to
write the employee ID which has been provided to you by the company, then you have to
enter the employee ID here, after that you have the
option of date of birth below, you have to click on it, then
here an interface will open in
which year will appear,
then month will appear, then date will appear, then you have to take the year, in
this way you can select the year by
pressing your thumb and scrolling, after that you have to take the month,
after taking the month you have to take the date,
after that you have to do it, then go to Add
Health Policy below, as soon as you click then in
this way you will
see the insurance card and all the members
of the family and their cards will be visible, you will normally
scroll it left right, so here
you have to select as much as you want in your family
Everyone's card will be visible if they are a member